Register of the Jerry Allan Rose papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Printed Matter, 1945-2006, undated
  - Publications featuring works by Rose, 1958-1965
    - The Saturday Evening Post, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 23: 6-9)
      Includes the March 23, 1963 issue featuring "I'm Hit! I'm Hit!"; the August 24, 1963 issue featuring "Laos: The War that Never Stops"; the November 2, 1963 issue featuring "'We Are Going to Change This Damn World!'"; and the March 28, 1965 issue featuring "Will Cambodia Go Communist?"
    - Time Inc., 1961-1962 (Box-folder 17: 1)
    - Time magazine, Vol. 79, No. 6, 1962 (Box-folder 17: 2)
      Contains photos of South Vietnamese forced laborers taken by Rose on page 27.
    - The Western Review, Vol. 23, 1959 (Box-folder 17: 3)
      Includes an author highlight on Jules Supervielle written by Jerry Rose.
  - Clippings, 1945-2006
    - Grant Wolfkill articles, 1945-1965 (Box-folder 17: 4)
    - The Saturday Evening Post articles, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 23: 10)
      Contains articles on South East and East Asian countries by various authors, mainly Stanley Karnow.
    - Vietnam War articles, 1965 (Box-folder 17: 5)
    - Vietnam and veterans articles, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 17: 6)
    - Vietnam Wall Visitor Center articles, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 17: 7)
  - Books, 1957-1960
    - Introduction to Spoken Vietnamese, 1957 (Box-folder 17: 8)
    - The Seventeenth Parallel by Duong Chau, 1958 (Box-folder 17: 9)
    - The Study of a Vietnamese Rural Community - Sociology by Gerald C. Hickey, 1960 (Box-folder 17: 10)
    - The Work Force in Saigon by James B. Hendry, 1960 (Box-folder 17: 11)
  - Booklets, 1956-1964
    - The Constitution of the Republic of Vietnam, 1958 (Box-folder 17: 12)
    - Land Reform Failures in Communist North Vietnam, undated (Box-folder 17: 13)
    - Montagnards of the South Vietnam Highlands, 1961 (Box-folder 17: 14)
    - Notes from the Underground: The Mystique of the Viet Cong, 1962 (Box-folder 17: 15)
    - Operation Exodus, undated (Box-folder 18: 1)
    - Provincial Government in Vietnam: A Study of Vinh Long Province by Jason L. Finkle, 1961 (Box-folder 18: 2)
    - Provisional Planning Report on Cam-Ranh Industrial Center, 1964 (Box-folder 18: 3)
    - The Review Horizons - Vietnamese Culture, undated (Box-folder 18: 4)
    - Saigon: A Booklet of Helpful Information for Americans in Vietnam, 1959 (Box-folder 18: 5)
    - Situation et Progrès, 1959 (Box-folder 18: 6)
    - Speeches by President Ngo Dinh Diem, 1956-1959 (Box-folder 18: 7)
    - Student Records from Vietnam, 1964 (Box-folder 18: 8)
    - Viet-Nam, 1961 (Box-folder 18: 9)
    - Vietnam Culture Series, 1961 (Box-folder 18: 10)
    - Vietnamese Legends, 1957 (Box-folder 18: 11)
    - What to Read on Vietnam: A Selected Annotated Bibliography, 1960 (Box-folder 18: 12)
  - Magazines, 1961-1965
    - National Geographic, Vol. 120, No. 4, 1961 (Box-folder 18: 13)
    - The New York Times Book Review, 1965 (Box-folder 23: 11)
      Includes a book review and spotlight on Wolfkill and Rose's novel Reported to Be Alive, titled "Man Does Survive," on page 38.
    - The Saturday Evening Post, Vol. 236, No. 15, 1963 (Box-folder 23: 12)
      Includes letters to the editor with praise for Rose's "I'm Hit! I'm Hit!" article from an earlier issue of The Saturday Evening Post.
    - Time magazine, Vol. 86, No. 15, 1965 (Box-folder 18: 14)
      Includes a segment in the "Books" section highlighting Wolfkill and Rose's book, Reported to Be Alive.
  - Pamphlets, 1958-1965
    - Sheet music, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 18: 15)
    - Vietnam tourist guides, 1958 (Box-folder 18: 16)
  - Vietnam map, 1956 (Box-folder 18: 17)